In the grim darkness of the far future there is only war.
Ultramarines: A Warhammer 40,000 Movie is a animation,
science fiction film directed by Martyn Pick.
A squad of Ultramarines answer a distress call from an Imperial Shrine World.
A full Company of Imperial Fists was stationed
there, but there is no answer from them.
The squad investigates to find out what has happened there.
Severus (voice), played by Terence Stamp.
Carnak, played by John Hurt.
Proteus (voice), played by Sean Pertwee.
Verenor (voice), played by Steven Waddington.
Pythol (voice), played by Donald Sumpter.
Nidon (voice), played by Johnny Harris.
Ultramarines: A Warhammer 40,000 Movie is a 2010 British adult animated action science fiction film set in Games
Workshop's fictional Warhammer 40,000 universe and based on the Ultramarines Chapter of the Space Marines.
Terence Stamp, Sean Pertwee, and John Hurt head the cast of voice actors, and
the screenplay was written by Black Library author Dan Abnett.
The film explores themes of space marine, demon,
adult animation, soldiers, warhammer.
The tone is thought_provoking.